manheim.com.au 2012-12-05

# Manheim Privacy Policy

You may receive details of vehicles to be sold by purchasing a catalogue from reception or downloading a We understand and appreciate the fact that our customers are concerned about the privacy afforded to their information collected when dealing with us. We are committed to providing our customers with a high level of privacy in relation to the personal information that is collected whilst dealing with Manheim. To display this commitment, we provide the following privacy statement for our customers' viewing. 

## Personal Information Collected

The type of information generally collected by Manheim includes your name, address, telephone number, facsimile number, e-mail address and photographic identification number. This information is collected in order for Manheim to perform the services that you have requested. As Manheim deals with motor vehicles, it is required under various legislation to accurately identify who is selling and purchasing vehicles through auction. For this reason we require and may verify information that identifies you when you intend to buy or sell through auction. 

## Information collected on this site

When you look at this website, our Internet Service Provider makes a record of your visit. The following information is logged for statistical purposes: 

  * your server address
  * your top level domain name (for example .com, .gov, .au, .nz, etc)
  * the date and time of your visit to the site 
  * the pages you accessed and documents downloaded 
  * the previous site you have visited 
  * the type of browser you are using 

We do not use or disclose your personal information collected for any other purpose other than the primary purpose without firstly gaining your consent, or where it is required by law. 

## Email

Your e-mail address is recorded only if you send an e-mail message to us. We respect the confidentiality of the information you provide to us. As such, any personal information that we collect will only be used for the purpose for which it has been provided to us. Under no circumstances will your e-mail address be added to a mailing list or used for any other purpose without your consent being obtained or where it is required by law. 

## Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

We do not use or disclose your personal information collected for any other purpose other than the primary purpose without firstly gaining your consent, or where it is required by law. 

In regard to our primary purpose, we act as an agent and we may disclose your personal information to the seller or purchaser of goods through auction when you consign or purchase through auction. This information is only disclosed if you successfully bid or sell goods through auction. 

## Data Quality

Our goal is to ensure that your personal information is accurate, complete and up-to-date. To assist us with this, please contact us if any of the details you have provided change. Further, if you believe that the information we have about you is not accurate, complete or up-to-date, contact us and we will use all reasonable efforts to correct the information. 

## Personal Information Security

Manheim is committed to keeping secure the data you provide us and we will take all reasonable precautions to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse or alteration. 

## Access to Personal Information

You can request us to provide you with access to the personal information we hold about you. If we are able to, we will provide you with access. A fee may apply to such access. If we deny your request for access, we will let you know why. Access is limited to our record of your address, contact details, photographic identification details, accounts with us and balances and statements relating to those accounts. 

## Cookies

This website makes use of both session and persistent browser cookies so that we can provide you with a secure member's page and ensure that you have read our Visitor Agreement. Cookies also let us perform statistical analysis in order to improve the website. We do not analyse individuals' behaviour. Any information that we collect is subject to our Privacy Policy. 

If you do not wish to receive cookies you may set your browser to refuse cookies. However this will mean that you are unable to take full advantage of the website's features. For example you will not be able to purchase vehicles online without logging in to every individual page. 

## Promotional Material

If you have registered to receive communications from us and later change your mind, you may contact us to have your name removed from our distribution lists. You have the following options to do this: 

  * You can send an e-mail to [privacy@manheim.com.au](mailto:privacy@manheim.com.au)
  * You can send mail to the following address: 

Manheim  
Attn: The Privacy Officer  
PO Box 34  
Altona North 3025  
Australia 

You may also view our privacy policy document at our office. This document sets out our policies on the management of your personal information. 

## Privacy Complaints

If you wish to make a complaint about any breach or potential breach of this privacy policy or the National Privacy Principles, you can contact us. 

  * You can send an e-mail to [privacy@manheim.com.au](mailto:privacy@manheim.com.au)
  * You can send mail to the following address: 

Manheim  
Attn: The Privacy Officer  
PO Box 34  
Altona North 3025  
Australia
